University of Connecticut 1998.0186
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1962-1972
  - 1971-1972
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 154:, Folder 2347)
    - Department Honors Fellow (Box 154:, Folder 2348)
    - Dodd, Thomas J. (Box 154:, Folder 2349)
    - Drugs (Box 154:, Folder 2350)
    - E (Box 154:, Folder 2351)
    - Education, School of (Box 154:, Folder 2352)
    - Education Commission of the States (Box 154:, Folder 2353)
    - Employment Authorizations (Box 154:, Folder 2354)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 154:, Folder 2355)
    - Environmental Studies (Box 154:, Folder 2356)
    - Etherington Report (Box 154:, Folder 2357)
    - Evans, John M. (Box 154:, Folder 2358)
    - Exhibits, University Committee on (Box 154:, Folder 2359)
    - Experimental College (Box 154:, Folder 2360)
    - F (Box 154:, Folder 2361)
    - Faculty - Alumni Center (Box 154:, Folder 2362)
    - Faculty for Rational Action (Box 155:, Folder 2363)
    - Faculty Publications (Box 155:, Folder 2364)
    - Faculty Standards Committee (Box 155:, Folder 2365)
    - Faculty Summer Fellowships (Box 155:, Folder 2366)
    - Financial Aid ( John Rapp, Director) (Box 155:, Folder 2367)
    - Finance and Control, State Department of ( Adolf G. Carlson, Commissioner) (Box 155:, Folder 2368)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 155:, Folder 2369)
    - Foreign Students (Box 155:, Folder 2370)
    - Freshman Seminar Program (Box 155:, Folder 2371-2372)
    - Friedman, Donald - Public Information Office (Box 155:, Folder 2373)
    - G (Box 155:, Folder 2374)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Provost) (Box 155:, Folder 2375)
    - Gay liberation (Box 155:, Folder 2376)
    - General Scholastic Requirement Committee> (Box 155:, Folder 2377)
    - Goodwin, Dorothy (Assistant Provost) (Box 155:, Folder 2378)
    - Graduate School (Dr. Thomas Malone, Dean) (Box 155:, Folder 2379-2380)
    - Graduate School Student Council (Box 155:, Folder 2381)
    - Grants (Box 155:, Folder 2382)
    - H (Box 156:, Folder 2383)
    - Hampton Associates (Box 156:, Folder 2384)
    - Handicapped Students (Box 156:, Folder 2385)
    - Hartford Branch ( Wilber Griswold, Director) (Box 156:, Folder 2386)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation (Box 156:, Folder 2387)
    - Hartford Training Teachers of Teachers (Box 156:, Folder 2388)
    - Health Center (Box 156:, Folder 2389)
    - Health Services - Storrs (Box 157:, Folder 2390)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (Box 157:, Folder 2391)
    - Hewes, Robert E. (Dean of Students) (Box 157:, Folder 2392)
    - Higher Education (Box 157:, Folder 2393)
    - Hill, John (University Attorney) (Box 157:, Folder 2394)
    - Historic District (proposed) (Box 157:, Folder 2395)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 157:, Folder 2396)
    - Housing and Food Services (Box 157:, Folder 2397)
    - Humor (Box 157:, Folder 2398)
    - I (Box 157:, Folder 2399)
    - Inaugurations (Box 157:, Folder 2400)
    - Inner College (Box 158:, Folder 2401)
    - Institute of Material Science ( Leonid Azaroff, Director) (Box 158:, Folder 2402)
    - Institute of Public Service (Box 158:, Folder 2403)
    - Institute of Urban Research (Box 158:, Folder 2404)
    - Institute of Water Resources ( William Kennard, Director) (Box 158:, Folder 2405)
    - Inter-Area Residence Hall Council (Box 158:, Folder 2406)
    - Interim Structure (Box 158:, Folder 2407)
    - International Silver Award Dinner (Box 158:, Folder 2408)
    - Invitations (Box 158:, Folder 2409-2412)
    - Invoices (Box 158:, Folder 2413)
    - J (Box 159:, Folder 2414)
    - Joint Council (Box 159:, Folder 2415)
    - Jones, Betty J. (Trustee) (Box 159:, Folder 2416)
    - Jorgensen, Mrs. Albert N., Jr. (Trustee) (Box 159:, Folder 2417)
    - Junior Year in France (Box 159:, Folder 2418)
    - K (Box 159:, Folder 2419)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 159:, Folder 2420)
    - Koppleman Scholarships (Box 159:, Folder 2421)
    - L (Box 159:, Folder 2422)
    - Labor Education Center (Box 159:, Folder 2423)
    - Land Acquisition (Box 159:, Folder 2424)
    - Law School (Box 159:, Folder 2425)
    - Liberal Arts and Science ( Robert Lougee, Dean) (Box 159:, Folder 2426-2427)
    - Library, Wilbur Cross ( John McDonald, Director) (Box 159:, Folder 2428)
    - Loeb Awards (Box 159:, Folder 2429)
    - Long-range Financial Planning Commission (Box 160:, Folder 2430)
    - Long-range Planning Committee> (Box 160:, Folder 2431)
    - Lupton, John M. (Trustee) (Box 160:, Folder 2432)
    - M (Box 160:, Folder 2433)
    - Management Information System (Box 160:, Folder 2434)
    - Manning, John (Box 160:, Folder 2435)
    - Marcus, Walter (Trustee) (Box 160:, Folder 2436)
    - Marland, Sidney (U.S. Commissioner of Education) (Box 160:, Folder 2437)
    - Marine Sciences Institute (Box 160:, Folder 2438)
    - McCormick, Joseph R. (Trustee) (Box 160:, Folder 2439)
    - McMahon, Brien - Lecture Series (Box 160:, Folder 2440)
    - Merlin Bishop Center (Box 160:, Folder 2441)
    - Metanoia (Box 160:, Folder 2442)
    - Minority Group Efforts (Box 160:, Folder 2443)
    - Moreland, Wallace S. (Assistant to the President) (Box 160:, Folder 2444)
    - Museum of Art ( Paul Rovetti, Director) (Box 160:, Folder 2445)
    - N (Box 160:, Folder 2446)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land - Grant Colleges (Box 160:, Folder 2447)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 160:, Folder 2448)
    - New Careers Program (Box 160:, Folder 2449)
    - Newcomer's Tea (Box 160:, Folder 2450)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 160:, Folder 2451)
    - New England Center for Continuing Education (Box 160:, Folder 2452)
    - New England Council (Box 161:, Folder 2453)
    - New England Council for Latin-American Studies (Box 161:, Folder 2454)
    - New England Research Applications Center (Box 161:, Folder 2455)
    - New England Presidents (Box 161:, Folder 2456)
    - New England Universities Children Exchange Program (Box 161:, Folder 2457)
    - Nielsen, Carl (Trustee) (Box 161:, Folder 2458)
    - Northeastern Research Center for Wildlife Diseases (Box 161:, Folder 2459)
    - Nursing, School of ( Eleanor Gill, Dean) (Box 161:, Folder 2460)
    - Ombudsman ( Charles Oliver) (Box 161:, Folder 2461)
    - Orientation Committee 1971 Faculty Advisor ( Jacqueline Seide) (Box 161:, Folder 2462)
    - Orr, William C. (Box 161:, Folder 2463)
    - P (Box 161:, Folder 2464)
    - PAYE Proposal (Box 161:, Folder 2465)
    - Personnel Services Division (Box 161:, Folder 2466)
    - Pharmacy, School of ( Arthur Schwarting, Dean) (Box 161:, Folder 2467)
    - Physical Therapy, School of ( John Allen, Dean) (Box 161:, Folder 2468)
    - Placement (Box 161:, Folder 2469)
    - Polish Studies Program (Box 161:, Folder 2470)
    - President's Commission on the Status of Women ( Dorothy Goodwin, chair) (Box 161:, Folder 2471)
    - President's Easter Egg Hunt (Box 161:, Folder 2472)
    - President's Emeritus Tea (Box 161:, Folder 2473)
    - President's reception and dinner (Box 161:, Folder 2474)
    - Professional Employees Association (Proposed) (Box 161:, Folder 2475)
    - Project leadership (Box 161:, Folder 2476)
    - Public Works Department, State (Box 161:, Folder 2477)
    - Purchasing (Box 161:, Folder 2478)
    - R (Box 161:, Folder 2479)
    - Radio-TV Center ( Stanley Quinn, Director) (Box 161:, Folder 2480)
    - Readmissions (Box 161:, Folder 2481)
    - Recycling Committee (Box 161:, Folder 2482)
    - Recommendations (Box 161:, Folder 2483)
    - Red Cross (Box 162:, Folder 2484)
    - Registrar ( Ronald Dickerson) (Box 162:, Folder 2485)
    - Reprints (Box 162:, Folder 2486)
    - Research Council (Box 162:, Folder 2487)
    - Registration: Printed Material (Box 162:, Folder 2488)
    - Traffic and Parking Committee (Box 163:, Folder 2489)
    - Tuition (Box 163:, Folder 2490)
    - U (Box 164:, Folder 2491)
    - UCONN Summer Program (Box 164:, Folder 2492)
    - Undergraduate Student Research Committee (Box 164:, Folder 2493)
    - Universities (Box 164:, Folder 2494)
    - University bookstore (Box 164:, Folder 2495)
    - University Chronicle (Box 164:, Folder 2496)
    - University Extension Advisory Commissions (Box 164:, Folder 2497)
    - University Orchestra, Band, and Choir (Box 164:, Folder 2498)
    - University Foundation (Box 164:, Folder 2499)
    - University Senate (Box 164:, Folder 2500-2501)
    - Upward Bound Program (Box 164:, Folder 2502)
    - Urban semester (Box 164:, Folder 2503)
    - U.S. Office of Education (Box 164:, Folder 2504)
    - V (Box 164:, Folder 2505)
    - Veterans (Box 164:, Folder 2506)
    - W (Box 164:, Folder 2507)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 164:, Folder 2508)
    - Waterbury Higher Education Complex (Proposed) (Box 164:, Folder 2509)
    - White House (Speeches, Fellowships, Correspondence) (Box 164:, Folder 2510)
    - WHUS (Box 165:, Folder 2511)
    - Wilson, Kenneth (Vice president) (Box 165:, Folder 2512)
    - WNHC-TV (Box 165:, Folder 2513)
    - Women (Box 165:, Folder 2514)
    - X, Y (Box 165:, Folder 2515)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 165:, Folder 2516)
- Series II: Campus Unrest, 1968-1971
  - AAUP Newsletter, Vol. IX, 1968 December (Box 166:, Folder 2617)
  - April 26 Movement, and H. D. B. Reply (Box 166:, Folder 2618)
  - Babbidge
    - Reply to Professor Larry S. Carney, 1969 March 26 (Box 166:, Folder 2619)
    - Reply to Professor Heis's letter with 123 signatures, 1969 March 6 (Box 166:, Folder 2620)
    - Norwich Rotary Club (Box 166:, Folder 2621)
    - Reply to Dr. Reed, 1969 March 26 (Box 166:, Folder 2622)
    - ROTC Statement (Box 166:, Folder 2623)
    - Statement, 1968 October 30 (Box 166:, Folder 2624)
    - Statement on Re-use of State Police, 1968 December 5 (Box 166:, Folder 2625)
    - Statement, University Senate (Box 166:, Folder 2626)
    - Statement (demonstrations) (Box 166:, Folder 2627)
    - Statement, 1970 May 10 (Box 166:, Folder 2628)
    - University Foundation and Alumni Council luncheon, 1968 November 12 (Box 166:, Folder 2629)
  - Bard, R.L. (School of Law) - Statement on equal time, Ch. 8 (Box 166:, Folder 2630)
  - Bowler, Larry - Case (Box 166:, Folder 2631)
  - Branches - Protesters, 1968 (Box 166:, Folder 2632)
  - Brover, Charles - Statement following Board of Trustees Meeting, 1969 January 25 (Box 166:, Folder 2633)
  - Board of Trustees - John Budds statement, 1968 December 18 (Box 166:, Folder 2634)
  - Budds, John J. - Statement, 1969 January 15 (Box 166:, Folder 2635)
  - Budds, John J. - Statement, Special Board of Trustees Meeting, 1969 January 25 (Box 166:, Folder 2636)
  - Budds, John J. - Housing, Sororities (Box 166:, Folder 2637)
  - Campus disorders (Box 166:, Folder 2638-2640)
  - Campus Unrest (Box 166:, Folder 2641)
  - Campus Unrest - other colleges (Box 167:, Folder 2642)
  - Channel 8: Editorial - four faculty members (Box 167:, Folder 2643)
  - Channel 24: Connecticut Issue - Homer Babbidge, 1968 November 17 (Box 167:, Folder 2644)
  - Committee of Five Report (Box 167:, Folder 2645)
  - Connecticut legislators - letters (Box 167:, Folder 2646)
  - Connecticut Resistance Movement ( Students for a Democratic Society) (Box 167:, Folder 2647)
  - “Constructive changes to ease campus tensions” (Box 167:, Folder 2648)
  - Court Case - Change of Venue to New Haven, 1969 April 17 (Box 167:, Folder 2649)
  - Dissident Students - President Nixon's statement (Box 167:, Folder 2650)
  - Disturbance on Campus (Box 167:, Folder 2651)
  - Dr. Dombrowski - Governor's office (Box 167:, Folder 2652)
  - Dow Chemical
    - Ballot (Dr. Phillip D. Jacklin) (Box 167:, Folder 2653)
    - Correspondence (Box 167:, Folder 2654)
    - Documents, 1967 (Box 167:, Folder 2655)
    - Incident - letters, 1967 (Box 167:, Folder 2656)
    - Story - The New Year (Box 167:, Folder 2657)
    - Release, 1968 (Box 167:, Folder 2658)
    - Dow “Special” - Alumnus (Box 167:, Folder 2659)
    - Statements, 1968 (Box 167:, Folder 2660)
  - Editorials -, 1968 (Box 167:, Folder 2661)
  - Faculty for Rational Action (Box 167:, Folder 2662)
  - Faculty - Statement of position (Box 167:, Folder 2663)
  - Federation of University Teachers (Box 167:, Folder 2664-2665)
  - Gant, Edward V. (Provost): Statement re. Olin-Mathieson (Box 167:, Folder 2666)
  - General Electric Interviews, 1969 December 15 (Box 167:, Folder 2667)
  - Goodwin, Dr. - Statements (Box 167:, Folder 2668)
  - Gould, S. B., Dr. - Statement on Dissenters (Box 167:, Folder 2669)
  - Graduate Student Council Resolution on Recruitment, 1968 November 8 (Box 167:, Folder 2670)
  - Gulley Hall Fracas, 1970 April 24 (Box 167:, Folder 2671)
  - Hewes' Statement re. Olin-Mathieson, 1968 November 30 (Box 167:, Folder 2672)
  - Joint Policy Committee (Box 167:, Folder 2673-2674)
  - Leggett: Statement to Hartford Times, 1969 January 22 (Box 167:, Folder 2675)
  - McCormick-Nielson Legislative Meeting (Box 168:, Folder 2676)
  - Moratorium, 1969 October 15 (Box 168:, Folder 2677)
  - Moratorium, 1969 November 15 (Box 168:, Folder 2678)
  - National Observer Article File, 1970 (Box 168:, Folder 2679)
  - Olin-Mathieson Disruption (Box 168:, Folder 2680)
  - Open Recruitment on Campus Petition (Box 168:, Folder 2681)
  - Outreach (Box 168:, Folder 2682)
  - Peace Corps Recruiting - Manning Statement, 1968 November 12 (Box 168:, Folder 2683)
  - Petitions, 1969 (Box 168:, Folder 2684)
  - President's Newsletter - Placement, 1968 November 30 (Box 168:, Folder 2685)
  - President's Newsletter - re. Dow Chemical, 1968 November 5 (Box 168:, Folder 2686)
  - President's statement, 1969 January 23 (Box 168:, Folder 2687)
  - President's Newsletter, re. 1/25/69 Board Meeting, 1969 January 27 (Box 168:, Folder 2688)
  - Protest letters - Mr. Budds, et al. (Box 168:, Folder 2689)
  - Recruitment Materials (Box 168:, Folder 2690)
  - Reed, Howard - Statement (Box 168:, Folder 2691)
  - Religious counselors - Letter to H.D.B., 1970 (Box 168:, Folder 2692)
  - Roach, Jack (Box 168:, Folder 2693)
  - SDS complaints (Box 168:, Folder 2694)
  - SDS Foes - Edward A. Haddad (Box 168:, Folder 2695)
  - SDS Worker - Student Alliance Strategy to SDS (Box 168:, Folder 2696)
  - Service Clubs - American Legion (Disruptions), 1968 (Box 168:, Folder 2697)
  - Social work, School of (Box 168:, Folder 2698)
  - Sousa House Incident (Box 168:, Folder 2699-2700)
  - Stevens, Gerald - Letter and Response (Box 168:, Folder 2701)
  - Strike, 1970 May 7 (Box 168:, Folder 2702-2708)
  - Strike: Letters Answered (Dr. Wilson) (Box 169:, Folder 2709)
  - Student and Faculty Statement, 1969 March 24 (Box 169:, Folder 2710)
  - Student and Faculty Committee on Recruitment (Box 169:, Folder 2711)
  - Student Protests (Box 169:, Folder 2712-2717)
  - Students - Arrests for protesting, Drugs (Box 169:, Folder 2718)
  - Students - Letters from (Box 169:, Folder 2719)
  - Student Senate Resolution on Recruitment, 1968 December 8 (Box 169:, Folder 2720)
  - Student Unrest (Box 170:, Folder 2721-2723)
  - Suit by Students Suspended during May Strike (Box 170:, Folder 2724)
  - Support Mail: re. Strike to Dr. Babbidge (Box 170:, Folder 2725)
  - Telegrams re. Faculty Four (Box 170:, Folder 2726)
  - Temporary injunction - Letters (Roach) (Box 170:, Folder 2727)
  - Thackerey, Russel I. - Recognition (by U of C), 1969 February 20 (Box 170:, Folder 2728)
  - TIAA (Box 170:, Folder 2729)
  - Towers Quadrangle Survey (Box 170:, Folder 2730)
  - Tuition (Box 170:, Folder 2731-2739)
  - Tuition (Box 171:, Folder 2740-2755)
  - Tuition (Box 172:, Folder 2756-2759)
  - Underground Report #9, 1968 December 5 (Box 172:, Folder 2760)
  - UConn Free Press (Box 172:, Folder 2762)
  - University Senate Resolution (Strike) (Box 172:, Folder 2763)
  - University Senate - Select Faculty Committee Report, 1968 November 8 (Box 172:, Folder 2764)
  - University Senate - Special Meeting, 1968 December 2 (Box 172:, Folder 2765)
  - White and Black concern for Black (Box 172:, Folder 2766)
  - Wilson's Statement, 1969 March 24 (Box 172:, Folder 2767)
  - Women Intolerance of Vindictive Educational Suppression - WIVES (Box 172:, Folder 2768)
- Series III: Wallace Moreland Files, 1964-1972
  - A (Box 173:, Folder 2769)
  - Admissions - Re. problem of college board scores, 1965 September (Box 173:, Folder 2770)
  - Admissions - Boy-Girl Ratio, 1964 (Box 173:, Folder 2771)
  - Admissions - Population of Cities (Box 173:, Folder 2772)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center ( James E. Lyons, Director) (Box 173:, Folder 2773)
  - Alpha Gamma Rho Correspondence (Dean Hewes) (Box 173:, Folder 2774)
  - Alumni Director ( Ben Johnson), 1965-1966 (Box 173:, Folder 2775)
  - Alumni Association, U of C, awards (Box 173:, Folder 2776)
  - Alumni Association - Liaison and Communications Committee ( Edric Bates, chair) (Box 173:, Folder 2777)
  - Alumni Dormitories - Dedication, 1968 May 18 (Box 173:, Folder 2778)
  - American Legion (Box 173:, Folder 2779)
  - Animal Experimentation (Box 173:, Folder 2780)
  - Anton, Stanley (Mrs.) (Box 173:, Folder 2781)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (Box 173:, Folder 2782)
  - Associated Student Government ( Paul Devine, President), 1971 (Box 173:, Folder 2783)
  - Athletics
    - Athletic Advisory Committee (Box 173:, Folder 2784)
    - Mr. Christian's Successor (President, Advisory Committee) (Box 173:, Folder 2785)
    - Baseball scandal, 1961 (Box 173:, Folder 2786)
    - ECAC-Yale “Langer” Case (Box 173:, Folder 2787)
    - ECAC Executive Council, 1966 (Box 173:, Folder 2788)
    - Hickey, James B. (Director of Athletics), 1966 (Box 173:, Folder 2789)
    - Telecasting of Sports, 1965-1969 (Box 173:, Folder 2790)
    - TV Coverage of Basketball and Football Games, 1970-1971 (Box 173:, Folder 2791)
    - WTIC: Football-Basketball Broadcasting Contract (Box 173:, Folder 2792)
    - Athletic Department ( J. O. Christian), 1964 (Box 173:, Folder 2793)
    - Barry, Phillip, Manager Department of Inter. Athl., 1966 (Box 173:, Folder 2794)
    - Sponsor party information (Box 173:, Folder 2795)
    - NCAA - TV Report (Box 173:, Folder 2796)
    - Thefts at UConn - Athletes (Box 173:, Folder 2797)
  - Austin, Joseph, 1967 (Box 173:, Folder 2798)
  - B (Box 173:, Folder 2799)
  - Babbidge, H. D. - Correspondence with WSM, 1964 (Box 173:, Folder 2800-2802)
  - Pifer letters sent by Babbidge - Replies (Box 173:, Folder 2803)
  - Statements prepared for Dr. Babbidge, 1964 (Box 173:, Folder 2804)
  - Babbidge, H. D., 1964 (Box 173:, Folder 2805)
  - 25th Anniversary celebration (Box 173:, Folder 2806)
  - Bailey, Clark (Box 173:, Folder 2807)
  - Bard, Isiah (Box 173:, Folder 2808)
  - Ballou visit to campus (Box 173:, Folder 2809)
  - Band - Trip to Europe (Box 173:, Folder 2810)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi and Tau Beta Sigma National Convention, Storrs (Box 173:, Folder 2811)
  - Band - SNETCO commercial, N.Y. Giants appearance (Box 173:, Folder 2812)
  - Banks, Arthur C., Jr., Dr. (President, Greater Hartford Community College) (Box 173:, Folder 2813)
  - Barnett, Dr. James - Profiles (Box 173:, Folder 2814)
  - Barron's Profile - U of C (Box 173:, Folder 2815)
  - Barlett Arboretum (Box 173:, Folder 2816)
  - Belden, L. Richard, 1964 (Box 173:, Folder 2817)
  - Benjamin, Charles - correspondence with Dr. Babbidge re. Flags presented by American Legion, 1965 (Box 173:, Folder 2818)
  - Black Administrators at UConn (Box 173:, Folder 2819)
  - Black History Week (Box 173:, Folder 2820)
  - Blackman, Samuel G. (Box 173:, Folder 2821)
  - Black Panthers - Campus, 1967 (Box 173:, Folder 2822)
  - Bloodmobile (Box 173:, Folder 2823)
  - Blue Bike Brigade (Box 173:, Folder 2824)
  - Bollen, Gerald T. (Landscape Engineer) (Box 173:, Folder 2825)
  - Borge, Victor - Concert, 1965 October 18 (Box 173:, Folder 2826)
  - Borge, Victor - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 173:, Folder 2827)
  - Borge, Victor - Scholarships, 1965 (Box 173:, Folder 2828)
  - Boy Scouts of America - Eastern Connecticut Council #76 (Box 173:, Folder 2829)
  - Brand, Dr. John P. (School of Agriculture) (Box 174:, Folder 2830)
  - Brewster, Kingman (Box 174:, Folder 2831)
  - Bridgeport Area Chamber of Commerce, 1964 December (Box 174:, Folder 2832)
  - Brock-Hall Daily Company (Box 174:, Folder 2833)
  - Brooks, Whitney L., Visit (Box 174:, Folder 2834)
  - Brotman, Michael (Auditorium Director), 1965-1966 (Box 174:, Folder 2835)
  - Brown, Freda (Box 174:, Folder 2836)
  - Buck, Raymond (University Publications) (Box 174:, Folder 2837)
  - University of Connecticut Chronicle Meetings, 1970 (Box 174:, Folder 2838)
  - Buckley Column - repercussions (Box 174:, Folder 2839)
  - Budget Requests (Box 174:, Folder 2840-2843)
  - Burglary Ring - UConn Students, 1963-1964 (Box 174:, Folder 2844)
  - Burr, Charles - Kiwanis Club (Box 174:, Folder 2845)
  - Business Administration, School of ( Robert O. Harvey, Dean) (Box 174:, Folder 2846)
  - C, 1963-1964 (Box 174:, Folder 2847)
  - Cairns, Bob (Dinner for) - Dr. Babbidge, Host (Box 174:, Folder 2848)
  - California “Earn, learn, and Reimburse” Law (Box 174:, Folder 2849)
  - Campbell, Robert F. (Box 174:, Folder 2850)
  - Campbell, Angus (Director ISR, University of Michiga) (Box 174:, Folder 2851)
  - Campus Disorder (Box 174:, Folder 2852)
  - Campus Tour Map (Box 174:, Folder 2853)
  - Capsule History - University of Connecticut (Box 174:, Folder 2853)
  - Carlson, John A., 1966 October 5 (Box 174:, Folder 2854)
  - Carroll, Charles R., Jr. (Vice President, Stop & Shop, Inc.) (Box 174:, Folder 2855)
  - (Student) Cars on Campus, 1971 (Box 174:, Folder 2856)
  - Cawley, John W., Dr. (Box 174:, Folder 2857)
  - Center for Economic Education (Box 174:, Folder 2858)
  - Center for the Environment and Man (Box 174:, Folder 2859)
  - Zampano Nomination for Junior Chamber of Commerce (Box 174:, Folder 2860)
  - Charter Oak Tree (Box 174:, Folder 2861)
  - Christian, J. O., Field Dedication (Box 174:, Folder 2862)
  - Chronicle, University of Connecticut, applicants for position as editor (Box 174:, Folder 2863)
  - Chronicle, Proposed (Box 174:, Folder 2864)
  - Civil Defense (Box 174:, Folder 2865-2866)
  - Clearing house and College Student Personnel Abstracts (Box 174:, Folder 2867)
  - Class tree planting, 1965 May (Box 174:, Folder 2868)
  - Coast Guard Research Facility at Avery point, Proposed (Box 174:, Folder 2869)
  - Co-ed Murder (Box 174:, Folder 2870)
  - College of Agriculture ( Edwin J. Kersting, Dean), 1967 (Box 174:, Folder 2871)
  - Connecticut Hospital Association (Box 174:, Folder 2872)
  - Dr. Bosworth, Irving Allen, Daniel Colfax (Meeting), 1967 January 18 (Box 174:, Folder 2873)
  - College Bowl, 1970 January 10 (Box 174:, Folder 2874)
  - Commission on the Age of Majority (Box 174:, Folder 2875)
  - Commission on the Arts - State (Box 174:, Folder 2876)
  - Commission on Study of Higher Education (Box 174:, Folder 2877)
  - Community Action Group (Box 174:, Folder 2878)
  - Compact for Education (Box 174:, Folder 2879)
  - Concern of the University Booklet Distribution (Box 174:, Folder 2880)
  - Conference on Technological Innovation - Storrs (Box 174:, Folder 2881)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Information Services (CAIS) (Box 174:, Folder 2882)
  - Connecticut Broadcasters Association Visit to UConn, 1964 April 28 (Box 174:, Folder 2883)
  - Connecticut Broadcasters Fall Convention, 1965 October 24 (Box 174:, Folder 2884)
  - Connecticut Comprehensive Health Planning Council (Box 174:, Folder 2885)
  - Connecticut Constitutional Government (Box 174:, Folder 2886)
  - Connecticut Daily Campus (Box 174:, Folder 2887)
  - CDC Old Editors Association (Box 174:, Folder 2888)
  - CDNA Meeting on Storrs Campus (Box 174:, Folder 2889)
  - Connecticut Farm Bureau (Box 174:, Folder 2890)
  - Connecticut Nurserymen's Association (Plant Connecticut Week) (Box 174:, Folder 2891)